neebo.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Neebo.com

  | 

### Privacy Policy

**Introduction** \- Nebraska Book Company, Inc. d/b/a Neebo (“Neebo” or “we”) is committed to protecting your privacy. Neebo has established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand the manner in which we collect and use your information and the efforts we use to protect it. Please note that this policy is for Neebo’s website only and does not apply to other third party websites that you may link from our website. Please check the privacy policies on those websites for more information. 

**Personal Information Collected**  
Neebo recognizes the need for consumers to control the use and management of personal information. “Personal information” means information that can be used to identify or contact an individual. This may include, but is not limited to, a first and last name, a physical address, an email address, a student id number, a phone number, and credit card information. If you are visiting our site to browse or find information about Neebo’s products or services, you do not need to provide any personal information. If you decide to make a purchase, participate in a Neebo promotion or submit a review or comment, however, we collect this information so that we can provide you with the product or service you requested or otherwise identify or contact you for purposes related to your order or participation. 

**Automatic Information Collected**  
Our website makes use of various technologies to collect information about types and versions of internet browsers used when accessing our website. This information and information about Internet IP addresses, as well as date and time web pages are visited, are stored in various security and traffic logs. Our service provider reviews these logs, using statistical analysis, in an effort to track and predict traffic patterns and estimate resource needs. Unless we are tracking down a technical problem or we suspect either fraudulent behavior or illegal conduct we do not trace specific user sessions. 

**Personal Information Use** Neebo uses personal information provided by you so that we can service your account. Also note that we may need to transfer that information to our agents or employees of our service providers. For example, we may need to provide your address to a wholesaler or a shipping company that will ship a product directly to you. We will not sell or trade your information to unrelated third parties without your prior consent . When you successfully submit a purchase order or promotion entry you will receive confirmation from our system. As your order status changes you may also receive notifications via email. These notifications are considered part of our service and may not be disabled. We may also periodically send you email notifications concerning products or services. Any such notification will include instructions for opting out of future mailings. Neebo uses IP addresses to analyze trends in website usage, administer the site, track user’s movements throughout the website and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Neebo will protect your privacy by NOT sharing your email address with anyone. When you ask a question, respond to a survey or place an order on-line, your email address will stay with Neebo. This degree of security means you will receive no correspondence unless it’s from Neebo. 

**Authorization** When you open an account or place an order on our website, you authorize Neebo to send you emails and/or SMS text messages that include information about discounts, deals and products. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time. Neebo may use information about you, including personal information and the information you provide for your on-line transaction and/or online account creation to: (1) allow you to participate in features offered or to provide related customer service, such as responding to questions, complaints or comments; (2) customize content recommendations and offers displayed to you; (3) process a transaction that you initiate; (4) provide you with information, products or services; (5) send you special offers from Neebo, its advertisers, or its third-party business partners; (6) improve services and for internal business purposes; (7) contact you with regard to use of the services and, in Neebo’s discretion, make changes to policies; and (8) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent. Neebo will not ask you for your personal information, account username, and password, or any of your credit or debit card information via email or text message, and you will not provide such information via email or text message. Neebo will have no responsibility for any misuse of such information if you provide such information via email or text message. 

**Third Parties** Neebo partners with third parties to provide various products and services. When you sign up for these services or products, Neebo will share only the personal information that is necessary for the third party to provide the product or service to you. We take reasonable steps to ensure that these third parties are obligated to protect your information on Neebo’s behalf. We will only transfer the information to the extent necessary to provide the requesting information, service or product to you, although we may release personal information if we are legally required to do so. If we are legally compelled to release information to a third party, Neebo may or may not notify you of this release at the discretion of Neebo, and will be based on the nature and conditions surrounding the release of information. 

**Information Control** Your customer profile is accessible from our website and you may update it at anytime. Our website provides you with the ability to change your phone numbers, physical addresses, and email address information stored in your profile. You may also write to us at the address listed at the bottom of this policy to request that we make the change for you. 

**Age of Users** The Site is targeted to college students. Individuals under the age of 18 (“Minors”) are not permitted to use the Site without the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms. If you are the parent or guardian agreeing to these Terms on behalf of a Minor, you are fully responsible for the Minor’s use of the Site, including all financial charges and legal liability that the Minor may incur. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account or to post personal information on our websites. Should we learn that someone under the age of 13 has provided any personal information to or on any of our Sites, we will remove that information as soon as possible. 

**Supplemental Technologies** Neebo’s website uses cookies, session identifiers, JavaScript™, and browser detection technology to provide consumers with a more pleasant online experience. Many browsers provide consumers with the ability to disable some or all of these technologies. Disabling them, especially in the case of JavaScript™, may prevent you from viewing some web pages. Note that the cookies we use do not place any personally identifiable information on your computer. Our site also does not participate in Ad Networks or use Web Bugs/Web Beacons to track consumer activity. 

**Confidentiality and Security** Neebo takes reasonable steps to ensure that your information is protected. On our website, we use industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting your personal information. Our website is hosted in a data center which makes use of multiple levels of redundant firewalls and database encryption to protect information. Internally, we limit access to your information to those employees or agents who we believe have a reasonable need to use the information to provide products or services to you, or to perform their jobs. 

**Secure Online Ordering** We have gone to great lengths to protect the security and validity of your credit card transaction. Our order forms are encrypted by our secure server to guarantee that the information can be read by us only. It will appear as indecipherable gibberish if the data is intercepted by an unauthorized source. We use the process developed by Mozilla-SSL (Secure Socket Layer)-to guard information. SSL is the industry standard for online security. Today's web browsers support this protocol, including Firefox, Microsoft Internet Explorer and others. Before a business can use SSL, it must be certified by an independent authority. This trusted third party will determine if the business is legitimate. VeriSign, one of the largest such companies in the world, certified us.

**How to Tell It's Secure** There are a couple of ways to tell if the information you are receiving is coming from a secure server.

  1. Check the security icon. Most browsers use a key (Firefox) or padlock (Microsoft Internet Explorer). An unbroken emblem indicates a secure browser.
  2. Check the URL field of your browser. With a secured server the address will begin with https:// instead of the usual http://.

**Notifications** When your order is placed on our website we will send you an email notification. When your order status changes you may also receive notifications via email. These notifications are considered part of our service and may not be disabled. We will send the email but we cannot guarantee delivery. You are responsible for providing a valid email address and for updating it when your address changes. Neebo may, depending on the importance and urgency of the notification, choose to contact you via telephone or postal mail. When doing so, we will use the phone number and/or address associated with your account or transaction. 

**Terms and Conditions** Please review Neebo.com’s Terms and Conditions which also governs to your visit to the Site and has additional information relevant to personal information. 

**History** A privacy policy was established for this website in 2008. Neebo periodically makes changes to the policy to reflect additions or changes to our practices. You may review the current policy at anytime by returning to this web page. This policy was last changed on March 29th, 2013. 

**Compliance** \- This privacy policy complies ecommerce industry best practice guidelines and with California's Privacy Protection Act of 2004. If you have any questions or concerns about this policy please contact Neebo using the information provided below. 

**Contact**  
For inquiries about the Privacy Policy email us: [legal@neebo.com](mailto:legal@neebo.com)  

Or by mail:

Neebo, Inc.  
Attn: Neebo.com Privacy Policy Issues  
4700 S. 19th Street  
Lincoln, NE 68512  

|    
---|---|---
